forex-trading247.com 2013-10-06

# Privacy Policy

Wealthsolutionsx.com [hereinafter referred to as "Company", "us" or "we"] collect personal information about you and distribute that information to provide you with services and products you request on this website. In addition, we distribute that information to others to provide you with other products and services. This summary and the full policy below describes how information is collected and distributed and your choices with respect to your personal information. Please review our full Privacy Policy for detailed information on our information and privacy practices.

Information We Collect and Retain Summarized: 

We collect your personal information and demographic information you choose to provide us. We also collect information about how you use our site and the areas of our site that you visit. We may also acquire information about you from third parties in order to further personalise your experience. The resulting logs that we create contain information necessary for us to analyse the use of resources, troubleshoot problems, and improve our services. We also use cookies and web beacons for tracking payments from you and to third parties.

How Your Information is Used:

Information you provide us upon registration for services and products listed on our site, post in public areas of the site, or placed in a searchable database will be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world. We use commercially reasonable practices to provide a safe, secure environment by limiting access to our database to authorised persons with whom we are in a contractual relationship, but cannot guarantee that unauthorised parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorised persons store or transfer information downloaded from the database, so you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information to our Site.

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, and to operate and improve our site. Our services may include the display of personalised content and advertising. We may use your information to contact you about site updates, conduct surveys, or informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

Disclosure of Information to Others:

We share your information with third parties who deliver the products and services you have requested. These third parties may not use your information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services.

We may also use your information to contact you about other products or services available from third parties. We may also share your information with third parties who may contact you about their products or services. We also share information where legally required. Information collected on our Sites is stored in whole or in part in the United States, and therefore subject to U.S. law. Finally, we may disclose and transfer information if our business is sold or acquired.

Your Choices About Your Information:

You may delete the personal information you submit to us at any time by notifying us at info@wealthsolutionsx.com . When you request us to delete your personal information, it will be deleted, but we will retain logs, demographic and statistical information about you and keep an archival copy of your information in an anonymous form. If your personal information was previously accessed by others or transferred to others using our Site, we are unable to delete the information from their systems.

We have no control over the information that Ad Networks or other third parties may have about you. We encourage you to visit their websites and review and read the privacy policies and opt-out practices that govern their usage.

If you change your mind about receiving communications from us, you may notify us of your preferences by info@wealthsolutionsx.com.   
You may also turn off cookies through your web browser. However, this may affect your use of our site as well as other's sites.

How to Contact Us: 

You may contact us for questions or concerns about our privacy practices by email to: info@wealthsolutionsx.com

The Complete Privacy Policy

Wealthsolutionsx.com is committed to advising you of the right to your privacy and strives to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Policy sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to this web site.

By registering or using this site, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Statement. Please read this Statement carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law. If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information, please do not use this website.

Scope of this Policy:

This policy applies to this website and regulates the processing of information relating to you and grants both us and you various rights with respect to your personal data. It describes what type of information we collect; how we use that information and to whom we can provide that information. It also informs you of how to notify us to stop using your information. Our company is located in the United States. You may be located in a country that has laws which are more restrictive about the collection and use of your personal information. However, by using our site, you agree to waive the more restrictive laws and agree to be governed by the laws of the United States.

This Site may also post links to other web sites over which we have no control. As such, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites when you choose to link from this site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

We also do not control the data use practices of those persons or entities who may access your information on this site for the purposes of providing the service or product you have requested or third party Ad Networks and other third parties with whom we work to serve you personalised ads on our site. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and opt-out choices of those third parties so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

Information We Collect and Retain: 

We collect the following general types of information about you when you visit and use our Site: personal information, demographic information, behavioural information, and indirect information. Sometimes we collect combinations of these types of information.

Personal information is information that can be used to identify you, or any other individual to whom the information may relate, personally. We do not collect personal information unless you choose to provide it to us. Some examples of personal information that we collect in some areas of our Site, depending on the services you use and local law, are: 

  * First and Last Name
  * Physical Address
  * Email address
  * Telephone number
  * Credit card number
  * Contact information
  * Billing information
  * Any other information you provide to use during the registration process or though the course of communicating with us about the products and services provided on the Site.

Demographic information is information that may or may not be unique to you in the sense that it refers to selected population characteristics, Such information may include, but is not limited to, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education, marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests.

Behavioural information is information pertaining to how you use our site, the areas of our site that you visit, what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software including your IP address, geographic location, browser preference, operating system type, domain names, times that you access the internet and other website you have been referred to us through. This information is necessary for analysing the use of resources, troubleshooting problems, preventing fraud, and improving our services and products.

Third party Information is information that we acquire from a third party which may include personal, demographic, behavioural and indirect information. We obtain this information so that we can personalise the advertising that is shown to you on our site.

Web Technology Information is information we automatically collect from you when you open one of our emails or visit our site. This includes information collected from the use of cookies, web beacons or java script.   
No Information Collected from Children:

We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Since we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. 

Credit Card Information and Bank Account Information:

We may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers, bank account information and related information when an individual places an order on wealthsolutionsx.com. When the credit card or bank account information is submitted to us, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL Encryption Software. We will use the credit card information or bank account information for purposes of processing and completing the transaction you requested on the Website, and the credit card information or bank account information will be disclosed to third parties as necessary to complete the requested purchase transaction.

Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and Java Script:

"Cookies" are a feature in your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of our Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of our website, you need to accept cookies.

We predominately use "session" cookies, which are not permanently stored on your hard drive. Session cookies expire after two hours of inactivity or when you close your browser. When you carry out the purchase of a service or a product on our website, a large amount of data is processed by our system and transferred through each page of the search or registration. This information includes all information you input on a registration page or questionnaire(s) you complete as part of the registration process as well as demographic information that is not unique to you. "Session" cookies allow us to keep track of this data until you have completed your search or registration.

We may use "persistent" cookies primarily to ensure that we do not show you pages that you have already seen and to personalise your site experience and save you time. "Persistent" Cookies enable us to recognize whether you have responded to any questionnaire or registration or have already been presented with an advertisement or information placed on the site so that we do not show you the same information again the next time you visit our site. The "persistent" cookies we use will remain on your computer after you have left our site and will expire when you log out of the Site or 60 days after your last visit for security cookies, 90 days after your last visit for payment tracking cookies, or two years after your last visit for advertisement cookies.

We may also allow other companies to display advertisements to you while you are visiting our Sites and your web browser must request these advertisements from those companies' servers. These companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. We have no control over the practices of those third party advertisers and are not responsible for their technology or tracking. We encourage you to review the policies of such advertisers when you link to their website.

Removing Cookies:

You have the ability to accept, decline or move cookies at any time by modifying your browser settings. Please see http://cookiecentral.com for more information on cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the web site.

Web Beacons:

We also use electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) that allow us to collect certain information about your visit to these Web pages (including the number of users who have visited those pages), measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements, and deliver services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique used to compile aggregated statistics about web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. This information may be shared with one or more third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Web pages, how those visitors use those Web Pages, and the effectiveness of their advertisements. We may also use web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in our database.

Disabling Web Beacons:

Because Web beacons are the same as any other content request, you cannot opt out or refuse them. However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.

JavaScript: 

We may also use JavaScript within certain advertisements. JavaScript is a computer language that enhances the functionality of websites, particularly in respect to pictures. We do not collecting any personal data via JavaScript but use it to analyse and improve the site's functions. 

Disabling JavaScript:

You may deactivate JavaScript via your browser settings or activate it the same way. If you disable JavaScript you will not be able to use some of the functions of the website.

IP Addresses:

We automatically track certain information based upon your behaviour on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

Computer Profiles: 

We may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyse the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, we may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, colour capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.

How We Use the Information Collected: 

Providing Services and Products. We use the information we gather on the Site for the purposes of providing the services and or products you have requested. This may include passing your information on to a third party with which we have a contract to provide such services. Although our contractual arrangement limits how such a third party can use your information, we do not control the privacy practices of this third party. If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from the third party's database, you will need to contact that party directly.

Improving our Website:

We use the information we gather on the Site to respond to any inquires you make; operate and improve our Site, improve and create a positive user experience; and deliver the products and services advertised on our Site. Our services include the display of personalised products, content, and advertising relating to your experience and interests. The information we gather on this Site may be shared with other companies under common ownership with ours throughout the world.

Public Posting: 

Information you post in public areas of the Site or place in the searchable database will be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world, including those in countries that might not have legislation that guarantees adequate protection of personal information as defined by your country of residence. By providing your personal information for inclusion in our database, you acknowledge that you consent to your information being used as described here. While we use commercial industry standards to safeguard your information from unauthorised access or inappropriate use by third parties, we do not control these third parties and we are not responsible for their use of information you post or otherwise make available in the public areas of our Site. Please be sure you do not post sensitive information in these areas.

Disclosure of Information to Others: 

We disclose to third parties throughout the world your personal information, combined personal, demographic, behavioural or indirect information, as set forth below: 

Product and Service Delivery: 

We may share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of products and services you have requested. We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ, to perform technical functions on our behalf. Examples include third parties who host our website, analyse our data, provide marketing assistance, process credit card payments, and provide customer service. These companies and individuals may not share that information with any other third party or use that data for any other purpose. 

Third Party Products and Services: 

We may disclose such information to third parties to provide you with information about the opportunities, products or services of third parties. We use the data and data logs we have about you, including interests and preferences you have expressed, to determine whether you might be interested in the opportunities, products or services of a particular third party. This type of marketing may be in the form of email offers or mobile offers sent to you by third parties or telemarketing calls from third parties. 

Anonymous information: 

We also share aggregated anonymous information about you and other persons using our Site with third parties so that they can understand the array of visitors to the Site and how those visitors use the Site. This includes demographic information and behavioural information.

Legal Process: 

We disclose information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion pursuant to a request from a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith - after considering your privacy interests and other factors - that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 

Acquisition or Merger: 

We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court. You will be notified of the sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party by email or through a prominent notice posted on the Site.

Again, in each of these situations, the recipients of your data may potentially be located in any country in the world.

Third Party Use of Your Information: 

Third parties also collect and use information about you on our Site in the following way: 

Advertiser cookies and web beacons - Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the Site and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about you. We do not control the use of such technology and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

Hyperlinks- Our Site and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. We do not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

Security Measures Undertaken

We endeavour to safeguard and protect your information. When you submit information on the website, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store Personal Information are kept in a secure physical environment. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, we use Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the Internet. Please be advised that, although we take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data at or through this site is at your own risk. However, access to your information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public.

Changes to Privacy Statement: 

We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Statement. We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

Your California Rights: 

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer's personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in this policy, you have agreed to allow us to share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes until you remove your information and thus, agreement for such disclosure. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on one of our sites or contact us via email to remove your information from our database. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing info@wealthsolutionsx.com. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

Terms and Conditions Explained

Should you have any further concerns or inquisitions you can refer to the Full Terms and Conditions here.
